https://americancollectors.com/terms-of-use/

Terms of Use
Terms of Use
Welcome to our website (the “site”), which is owned and operated by American Collectors Insurance (American Collectors Insurance). American Collectors Insurance maintains the site as a service to its visitors, subject to the following terms and conditions concerning the privacy policy of the Site (“Privacy Policy”). When you use the Site, you understand and adhere to the privacy policy. American Collectors Insurance reserves the right to modify content on the site periodically without prior notice.
You may view, download, and print contents from the site subject to the following conditions: (a) the content may be used solely for information purposes; and (b) the content may not be modified or altered in any way. You may not republish, distribute, prepare derivative works, or otherwise use the content other than as explicitly permitted herein.
You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to enclose any trademark, logo, or other proprietary information (including images, text, page layout, or form) of American Collectors Insurance without the express written consent of American Collectors Insurance. You may not use any meta tags or any other “hidden text” utilizing American Collectors Insurance name or trademarks without the express written consent of American Collectors Insurance. You may not use any American Collectors Insurance logo or other proprietary graphic or trademark as part of the link without express written permission.
You may submit comments and provide other content so long as the content is not obscene, illegal, threatening, or defamatory and so long as the content does not invade the privacy or infringe the intellectual property of a third party. Further, such content may not contain software viruses, mass mailings, chain letters, or any form of “spam.” You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of the information.
By submitting information, you grant American Collectors Insurance a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sub-licensable right to reproduce, use, modify, publish, adapt, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. By submitting information you also represent and warrant that that the content is accurate; you own or have permission to use the content that you submit; and that use of the content will not cause injury to any person or entity.
The Site and all the content within the Site are the property of American Collectors Insurance and are protected by United States copyright laws and international treaty provisions. The compilation, organization and display of the content as well as all software and inventions used on and in connection with this site are the exclusive property of American Collectors Insurance.
American Collectors Insurance and other marks indicated on our site are registered trademarks of American Collectors Insurance in the United States and/or other countries. Other American Collectors Insurance marks, graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts noted on the Site are American Collectors Insurance service marks, trademarks and trade dress and are the sole and exclusive property of American Collectors Insurance. American Collectors Insurance service marks and trademarks may not be used in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, in any manner that disparages or discredits American Collectors Insurance and in connection with any service or product that is not sponsored, endorsed or produced by American Collectors Insurance. All other trademarks not owned by American Collectors Insurance or its subsidiaries that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by American Collectors Insurance.
Because we respect your right to privacy, we have developed a Privacy Policy to inform you about our privacy practices. Please view the Privacy Policy (https://americancollectors.com/privacy-policy) to learn more about the company’s privacy guidelines.
The Site may provide hyperlinks to third party websites or access to third party content. American Collectors Insurance does not control, endorse, or guarantee content found in such sites. You agree that American Collectors Insurance is not responsible for any content, associated links, resources, or services associated with a third party site. You further agree that American Collectors Insurance shall not be liable for any loss or damage of any sort associated with your use of third party content. Links and access to these sites are provided for your convenience only.
EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED IN AN AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND American Collectors Insurance, ALL CONTENT, SERVICES, AND PRODUCTS PROVIDED ON THIS WEB SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. American Collectors Insurance DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR THE APPROPRIATENESS OF THE SITE, ITS CONTENT, AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES OFFERED BY ON THE SITE FOR YOUR INTENDED USE. American Collectors Insurance DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SITE, ITS CONTENT, OR THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES IT OFFERS ON THE SITE MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS. SUBJECT TO THE TERMS OF ANY AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND American Collectors Insurance, American Collectors Insurance SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN DAMAGES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless American Collectors Insurance, employees, attorneys, and agents (“Indemnitees”) against all claims, expenses, liabilities, losses, costs, and damages, including reasonable attorney’s fees, that the Indemnitees may incur (i) in connection with your use of the site or any hyperlinked web site or (ii) resulting from content you supply.
All matters relating to your access to and use of the Site shall be governed by U.S. federal law or the laws of the States of where the specific website you are viewing is hosted without regard to its conflict of law principles. Any legal action or proceeding relating to your access to or use of the Site shall be instituted in a state or federal court of Pennsylvania.
If you have any questions regarding these Terms and Conditions, please contact American Collectors Insurance at info@americancollectors.com.
Email Address*
CAPTCHA
1-800-360-2277
info@americancollectors.com
(Column 1)
(Column 2)
(Column 3)
